[
    {
        "question": "A set of routines, standards, protocols, and tools for building software applications to access a web-based software application or web tool.",
        "answer": "API"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most essential representation of data (zero or one) at Layer 1 of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model.",
        "answer": "Bit"
    },
    {
        "question": "transmission is a one-to-many (one-to-everyone) form of sending internet traffic.",
        "answer": "Broadcast"
    },
    {
        "question": "is a unit of digital information that most commonly consists of eight bits.",
        "answer": "Byte"
    },
    {
        "question": "A model for enabling ubiquitous, convenient, on-demand network access to a shared pool of configurable computing resources (e.g., networks, servers, storage, applications, and services) that can be rapidly provisioned and released with minimal management effort or service provider interaction.",
        "answer": "Cloud Computing"
    },
    {
        "question": "A system in which the cloud infrastructure is provisioned for exclusive use by a specific community of consumers from organizations that have shared concerns (e.g., mission, security requirements, policy and compliance considerations). It may be owned, managed and operated by one or more of the organizations in the community, a third party or some combination of them, and it may exist on or off premises.",
        "answer": "Community Cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "The opposite process of encapsulation, in which bundles of data are unpacked or revealed",
        "answer": "De-encapsulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "The prevention of authorized access to resources or the delaying of time-critical operations. (Time-critical may be milliseconds or it may be hours, depending upon the service provided.)",
        "answer": "Denial Of Service"
    },
    {
        "question": "This acronym can be applied to three interrelated elements: a service, a physical server and a network protocol.",
        "answer": "DNS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Enforcement of data hiding and code hiding during all phases of software development and operational use. Bundling together data and methods is the process of encapsulation; its opposite process may be called unpacking, revealing, or using other terms. Also used to refer to taking any set of data and packaging it or hiding it in another data structure, as is common in network protocols and encryption.",
        "answer": "Encapsulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "The process and act of converting the message from its plaintext to ciphertext. Sometimes it is also referred to as enciphering. The two terms are sometimes used interchangeably in literature and have similar meanings",
        "answer": "Encryption"
    },
    {
        "question": "The internet protocol (and program) used to transfer files between hosts.",
        "answer": "FTP"
    },
    {
        "question": "An attacker fragments traffic in such a way that a system is unable to put data packets back together.",
        "answer": "fragment attack"
    },
    {
        "question": "The physical parts of a computer and related devices.",
        "answer": "Hardware"
    },
    {
        "question": "A combination of public cloud storage and private cloud storage where some critical data resides in the enterprise's private cloud while other data is stored and accessible from a public cloud storage provider.",
        "answer": "Hybrid Cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "The provider of the core computing, storage and network hardware and software that is the foundation upon which organizations can build and then deploy applications",
        "answer": "IaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "An IP network protocol standardized by the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) through RFC 792 to determine if a particular service or host is available.",
        "answer": "ICMP"
    },
    {
        "question": "Standard protocol for transmission of data from source to destinations in packet-switched communications networks and interconnected systems of such networks.",
        "answer": "IPV4"
    },
    {
        "question": "An attack where the adversary positions himself in between the user and the system so that he can intercept and alter data traveling between them.",
        "answer": "Man-in-the-middle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Part of a zero-trust strategy that breaks LANs into very small, highly localized zones using firewalls or similar technologies. At the limit, this places firewall at every connection point.",
        "answer": "Microsegmentation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Purposely sending a network packet that is larger than expected or larger than can be handled by the receiving system, causing the receiving system to fail unexpectedly.",
        "answer": "Oversized Packt Attack"
    },
    {
        "question": "The primary action of a malicious code attack.",
        "answer": "Payload"
    },
    {
        "question": "An information security standard administered by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council that applies to merchants and service providers who process credit or debit card transactions.",
        "answer": "PCI DSS"
    },
    {
        "question": "The web-authoring or application development middleware environment that allows applications to be built in the cloud before they're deployed as SaaS assets.",
        "answer": "PaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "The phrase used to describe a cloud computing platform that is implemented within the corporate firewall, under the control of the IT department. A private cloud is designed to offer the same features and benefits of cloud systems, but removes a number of objections to the cloud computing model, including control over enterprise and customer data, worries about security, and issues connected to regulatory compliance.",
        "answer": "private cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "A set of rules (formats and procedures) to implement and control some type of association (that is, communication) between systems.",
        "answer": "Protocols"
    },
    {
        "question": "Representation of data at Layer 3 of the Open Systems Interconnection (OSI) model.",
        "answer": "Packet"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cloud infrastructure is provisioned for open use by the general public. It may be owned, managed, and operated by a business, academic, or government organization, or some combination of them. It exists on the premises of the cloud provider.",
        "answer": "Public Cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "The standard communication protocol for sending and receiving emails between senders and receivers.",
        "answer": "SMTP"
    },
    {
        "question": "Computer programs and associated data that may be dynamically written or modified during execution.",
        "answer": "Software"
    },
    {
        "question": "The cloud customer uses the cloud provider's applications running within a cloud infrastructure. The applications are accessible from various client devices through either a thin client interface, such as a web browser or a program interface.",
        "answer": "SaaS"
    },
    {
        "question": "Faking the sending address of a transmission to gain illegal entry into a secure system.",
        "answer": "Spoofing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Internetworking protocol model created by the IETF, which specifies four layers of functionality: Link layer (physical communications), Internet Layer (network-to-network communication), Transport Layer (basic channels for connections and connectionless exchange of data between hosts), and Application Layer, where other protocols and user applications programs make use of network services.",
        "answer": "Transport Control Protocol/Internet Protocol (TCP/IP) Model"
    },
    {
        "question": "A virtual local area network (VLAN) is a logical group of workstations, servers, and network devices that appear to be on the same LAN despite their geographical distribution",
        "answer": "VLAN"
    },
    {
        "question": "A virtual private network (VPN), built on top of existing networks, that can provide a secure communications mechanism for transmission between networks.",
        "answer": "VPN"
    },
    {
        "question": "A wireless area network (WLAN) is a group of computers and devices that are located in the same vicinity, forming a network based on radio transmissions rather than wired connections. A Wi-Fi network is a type of WLAN.",
        "answer": "WLAN"
    },
    {
        "question": "The graphical user interface (GUI) for the Nmap Security Scanner, an open-source application that scans networks to determine everything that is connected as well as other information.",
        "answer": "Zenmap"
    },
    {
        "question": "Removing the design belief that the network has any trusted space. Security is managed at each possible level, representing the most granular asset. Microsegmentation of workloads is a tool of the model.",
        "answer": "Zero Trust"
    }
]